[Music]
hi my name is vikramjit Singh and I'm
currently pursuing my PhD I'm an
international business and marketing
from Jim's rohini Sector 5 and I'm very
happy to announce that currently I'm
placed in ICICI Lombard as a key
relationship manager
so I completed my graduation during the
pandemic time and I am a product of the
online education system who had no idea
what to do and how to do it so MBA was
never a choice for me it was a necessity
since in India even to get married you
need an MBA certificate now please bear
with my language but two years back when
I came to this college I came as a
donkey with an aspiration to become a
horse but the amount of efforts that my
faculty members have put into me I can
proudly say that after this journey of
two years I am a professional human
who's ready to take up the corporate
world
I think I've seen my graph in the last
two years go from here to here for
instance I mean I was a person for whom
even to talk in English for like two
minutes was a challenge in itself I
remember going to McDonald's gave me
shivers right now we are sitting in an
interview and I think I'm speaking well
so that is an achievement in itself in
the last two years I got into an
environment where I had ample of
opportunities I participated in cultural
activities I participated in debates and
all that stuff so this is something
which has actually helped me grow also I
would like to emphasize that the faculty
members over here are so supportive not
not only professionally but even if you
have a personal problem they are always
your go-to person
now I would like to share a dilemma
which I was in two years back which is
whether to pursue your phdm or not trust
me I'm done I'm almost done with my pcdm
and I still don't have an appropriate
answer to that but what I know is if yes
you wish to pursue your phdm then I
think gyms is a superb choice